    ID   Icon     Name                                                                                           Description                                                                                      Info                        
 5000000      Brown Kitty  They are quiet and gentle in nature, so they don't go craving for food too often. They don't seem to be too obedient of their owners.                                                                              
 5000001      Brown Puppy  They are outgoing and active in nature, so they can't sit still for a period of time, which makes them hungry often. They are very obedient of their owners.                                                       
 5000002      Pink Bunny   They are well-behaved and quiet, so they don't need to be fed more than the usual amount. They are smart and obedient, but also stubborn.                                                                          
 5000003      Mini Kargo   They are very very active, so they get hungry pretty often. Very intelligent, they are quite obedient of their owners.                                                                                             
 5000004      Black Kitty  They are quiet and gentle in nature, so they don't go craving for food too often. They don't seem to be too obedient of their owners.                                                                              
 5000005      White Bunny  They are well-behaved and quiet, so they don't need to be fed more than the usual amount. They are smart and obedient, but also stubborn.                                                                          
 5000006      Husky        Active, yet calm at times. Can be moderately fed. Very smart in general.                                                                                                                                           
 5000007      Black Pig    Very active and hungry at all times. Need to be fed often. Very friendly in nature, so it's easy to increase the level of closeness with it.                                                                       
 5000008      Panda        Calm, relaxed, and gentle. A very rare creature.                                                                                                                                                                   
 5000009      Dino Boy     A very adorable male baby dinosaur that is both active and unpredictable.                                                                                                                                          
 5000010      Dino Girl    A very adorable female baby dinosaur that is both active and unpredictable.                                                                                                                                        
 5000011      Monkey       The always-curious monkey never rests, wanders around.                                                                                                                                                             
 5000012      White Tiger  They are very gentle and obedient in nature, easily becoming friendly with the owner, which in turn speeds up the level-up process.                                                                                
 5000013      Elephant     Very outgoing and mature; doesn't need to be fed all the time. An intelligent pet that easily understands the commands from the master.                                                                            
 5000014      Rudolph      Every Christmas, Santa Claus rides on the sleigh driven by his trusty sidekick, Rudolph.                                                                                                                           
 5000015      Dasher       They are smart and obedient by nature, picking up commands faster than other pets, but they also can get hungry in a hurry.                                                                                        
 5000017      Robot        A hyper-active robot that always changes its mind on everything. Very unpredictable, yet easy to please.                                                                                                           
 5000018      Husky        Active, yet calm at times. Can be moderately fed. Very smart in general.                                                                                                                                           
 5000020      Mini Yeti    A trustworthy pet that quietly watches everyone's back. Quiet, but smart and gets a lot of things done.                                                                                                            
 5000021      Monkey       Very charming who is also very intuitive, but not as obedient as some of the others                                                                                                                                
 5000022      Turkey       Somewhat active, quiet and not well-behaved in nature. It is not very obedient, but isn't hungry very often.                                                                                                       
 5000023      Penguin      Penguins are always energetic and in good spirits. Use the Meso Magnet and Item Pouch on the Penguin to pick up the mesos and items on the ground.                                                                 
 5000024      Jr. Balrog   A trustworthy pet who is equally quick-witted. Unlike its masculine appearance, it is prone to insecurity and shyness.                                                                                             
 5000025      Golden Pig   This designed Golden Pig will definately bring you a Good Luck! Use the Meso Magnet and Item Pouch to pick up the mesos and items on the ground.                                                                   
 5000028      Dragon       A special egg that becomes a mythical Baby Dragon upon hatching.                                                                                                                                                   
 5000029      Baby Dragon  A Baby Dragon hatched out of the special Dragon Egg. At Level 15, the pet can be evolved into a full-fledged Adult Dragon with the help of Garnox the NPC using the Rock of Evolution.                             
 5000030      Green Dragon Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Dragon into a Green Dragon!                                                                                                                     
 5000031      Red Dragon   Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Dragon into a Red Dragon!                                                                                                                       
 5000032      Blue Dragon  Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Dragon into a Blue Dragon!                                                                                                                      
 5000033      Black Dragon Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Dragon into the rare and majestic Black Dragon!                                                                                                 
 5000034      Black Bunny  They are well-behaved and quiet, so they don't need to be fed more than the usual amount. They are smart and obedient, but also stubborn.                                                                          
 5000036      Jr. Reaper   Miniature death incarnate. Makes for a loyal but cheeky sidekick that is prone to talking back.                                                                                                                    
 5000037      Husky        Active, yet calm at times. Can be moderately fed. Very smart in general.                                                                                                                                           
 5000039      Porcupine    A small, furry creature with very, very sharp spikes. A lovable pet.                                                                                                                                               
 5000041      Snowman      An adorable Snowman that is also very active. May seem a little rude at times, but the more it is loved, the more affable it becomes.                                                                              
 5000044      Orange tiger They are very gentle and obedient in nature, easily becoming friendly with the owner, which in turn speeds up the level-up process.                                                                                
 5000045      Skunk        Calm and quiet by nature, the easy-going, eccentric Skunk has a rather humorous and pompous outlook on life, the finer things are what it enjoys.                                                                  
 5000047      Robo         A special egg that becomes a mythical Robo upon hatching.                                                                                                                                                          
 5000048      Baby Robo    A Baby Robo hatched out of the special Capsule. At Level 15, the pet can be evolved into a full-fledged Adult Robo with the help of Garnox the NPC using the Rock of Evolution.                                    
 5000049      Blue Robo    Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Robo into a Blue Robo!                                                                                                                          
 5000050      Red Robo     Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Robo into a Red Robo!                                                                                                                           
 5000051      Green Robo   Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Robo into a Green Robo!                                                                                                                         
 5000052      Gold Robo    Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Robo into a Gold Robo!                                                                                                                          
 5000053      Gorilla Robo Mysterious magical powers aligned and sucessfully evolved the Baby Robo into the rare and majestic Gorilla Robo!                                                                                                   
